What do you think?
What did you say?
Do you think what I said makes sense?
Sorry.
I wasn't listening carefully just now.
So you mean
we must find this codebook
to decrypt the message?
Encryption methods can often
reveal a person's character.
If you are ever in danger,
you can use your favorite book as a codebook.
It's getting late.
I'll go cook first.
Shiya.
Hello?
Mr. Pei,
the old man is awake.
Grandpa is awake.
Okay.
I'll go right away.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, you're awake.
How are you feeling?
Songsong is here.
Shiya.
Slow down.
Careful.
How is it, Grandpa?
Songsong,
let me ask you.
Do you know what Xiaoning has been busy with lately?
Probably nothing much.
I guess he's just messing with his hobbies.
Look at you as an older brother.
You should care more about your younger brother.
Grandpa,
did something happen?
Xiaoning...
Grandpa, I have some things to do.
I'll be leaving first.
Let Pei Song keep you company.
Songsong.
Yes, Grandpa.
Do you know
the relationship between Xiaoning and Shiya?
They were college classmates.
Xiaoning
had a crush on Shiya before.
You knew about this?
I only found out later.
Then why did you still marry Shiya?
Because I love her.
You love her.
So you knew her before.
I've known her for a long time.
What a sin,
my child.
Grandpa.
Why did you suddenly
pass out the other day?
Did something happen?
I saw the other day
that Ningning developed an AI
exactly like Shiya.
How could such a thing happen to the Pei family?
Where does this leave
the Pei family's dignity?
I'm so mad!
All of this,
what exactly is going on?
The IP address has been successfully cracked.
I'll wait for you at home.
When did you come back?
A while ago.
Don't you need to keep Grandpa company today?
I missed you.
Where are you running?
Run!
Why did you gamble if you have no money?
This...
How is this possible?
Bro.
This is a black card.
I just spent 200,000 on it last night.
You must have made a mistake.
Try swiping it again.
Are you messing with me?
I wouldn't dare.
My brother-in-law gave me this card.
My brother-in-law is Pei Song.
The Pei Song from the Pei Group.
I don't care about Pei or Zhang.
I
only care about money.
Wait a minute, bro.
Wait.
I'll call and ask
what's going on.
If not,
I'll have him bring you the money.
Hurry up and call.
No answer.
Beat him.
Within a week.
If you don't pay within a week,
your family can prepare for your funeral.